A Guide to the Papers and Photographs of Jackson Davis 1906-1947, and n.d.
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Glass Lantern Slides, 224 individual slides. (Box 12a-15a)
  - Labelled Slides (Box 12a-13a)
    - Slides of Southern Schools, L-1151 - L-1202 (Box 12a-13a)
      - Caroline County (Va) Training School, 1921, L-1186 (Box 13a)
      - Cemetery Cleaning; Charles City Co., Va. 1912, L-1187 (Box 13a)
      - Garden; Charles City County, Va. 1912, L-1188 (Box 13a)
      - Canning Display; Chesterfield, Va. 1912, L-1189 (Box 13a)
      - Old School; Baylorsville, Caroline Co., Va., L-1190 (Box 13a)
      - Caroline C.T.S.; Bowling Green, Va. 1919, L-1191 (Box 13a)
      - Canning Display; Cumberland Co., Virginia, L-1192 (Box 13a)
      - Canned Goods; Cumberland Co., Virginia, L-1193 (Box 13a)
      - Frazier's House; Gloucester Co., Virginia, L-1194 (Box 13a)
      - J.D. Eggleston at Holdcroft, Va. 1912, L-1195 (Box 13a)
      - Workshop; Shelby Co. (Va.) Training School, L-1196 (Box 13a)
      - Dormitory Construction; Shelby Co., Va. 1919, L-1197 (Box 13a)
      - Dormitory; Shelby Co. (Va.) Training School, L-1198 (Box 13a)
      - Shelby County (Va.) Training School, L-1199 (Box 13a)
      - Shelby County (Va.) Training School, L-1200 (Box 13a)
      - New Two Room Graded School; Waverly, Virginia, L-1201 (Box 13a)
      - New High School, $3,000.00; Sparta, Virginia, L-1202 (Box 13a)
    - Classes at the Hampton (VA) Institute, L1203 - L-1218 (Box 13a)
      - Cooking Class 1910, L-1203 (Box 13a)
      - Domestic Science Work: Caning Chairs, L-1204 (Box 13a)
      - Girl Cutting Out Dress Patterns, L-1205 (Box 13a)
      - Dressmaking Class, L-1206 (Box 13a)
      - Ironing 1910, L-1207 (Box 13a)
      - Domestic Science Work: Mattress Making, L-1208 (Box 13a)
      - Printing Office 1906, L-1209 (Box 13a)
      - Paint Shop, L-1210 (Box 13a)
      - Manual Training Work: Joinery Class, L-1211 (Box 13a)
      - Wheelwright Shop 1910, L-1212 (Box 13a)
      - Trade School Plastering Department, L-1213 (Box 13a)
    - Farming Scenes, L-1203 - L-1218 (Box 13a)
      - Boy in Dairy, L-1214 (Box 13a)
      - Old-Time Unimproved Country Well, L-1215 (Box 13a)
      - Planting Vegetables, L-1216 (Box 13a)
      - Plowing, L-1217 (Box 13a)
      - Modern Well, L-1218 (Box 13a)
  - Unlabelled Slides, L-1219 - L-1374 (Box 13a-15a)
    - Miscellaneous Farm Scenes, L-1219 - L-1253 (Box 13a-14a)
      - Bibb County Training School, L-1219 (Box 13a)
      - Miscellaneous Farms and Fields, L-1220 - L-1222 (Box 13a)
      - Pigs, L-1223 (Box 13a)
      - Field Laborers, L-1224 - L-1236 (Box 13a)
      - Miscellaneous Farm Scenes, L-1237 - L-1240 (Box 13a)
      - Produce and Goods, L-1241 - L-1253 (Box 13a-14a)
    - Group Activities, L-1254 - L-1257 (Box 14a)
      - Parades, L-1254, L-1255 (Box 14a)
      - Track Meets, L-1256 (Box 14a)
      - Children Playing, L-1257 (Box 14a)
    - Classes, L-1258 - L-1266 (Box 14a)
      - Chair Caning Class, L-1258 (Box 14a)
      - Music Assembly, L-1259 (Box 14a)
      - Cooking Classes, L-1260 - L-1265 (Box 14a)
      - Sewing Class, L-1266 (Box 14a)
    - Group Photos, L-1267 - L-1327 (Box 14a)
      - Miscellaneous Group Photos, L-1267 - L-1280 (Box 14a)
      - Unlabelled Portraits and Unposed Shots, L-1281 - L-1289 (Box 14a)
      - Students Before Their Schoolbuildings, L-1290 - L-1327 (Box 14a)
    - Buildings, L-1328 - L-1374 (Box 15a)
      - Schoolhouses, L-1328-1346 (Box 15a)
      - Cabins, L-1347 - L-1354 (Box 15a)
      - Houses, L-1355 - L-1371 (Box 15a)
      - Churches, L-1372 - L-1374 (Box 15a)
- Card File (Othertype 92-95)
  These are individual index cards kept by Davis to organize by subject the negatives he created.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject.